<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Top Post</title>
    <link>https://nygma.pro/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Top Post</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:37:51 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://nygma.pro/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Firstpost</title>
      <link>https://nygma.pro/posts/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:37:51 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nygma.pro/posts/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my first post here on hugo.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Africa is the world&amp;rsquo;s second-largest and second-most populous continent after Asia. At about 30.3 million km2 (11.7 million square miles) including adjacent islands, it covers 20% of Earth&amp;rsquo;s land area and 6% of its total surface area.[9] With nearly 1.4 billion people as of 2021, it accounts for about 18% of the world&amp;rsquo;s human population. Africa&amp;rsquo;s population is the youngest among all the continents;[10][11] the median age in 2012 was 19.7, when the worldwide median age was 30.4.[12] Based on 2024 projections.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Africa&amp;rsquo;s population will exceed 3.8 billion people by 2100.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;[13] Africa is the least wealthy inhabited continent per capita and second-least wealthy by total wealth, ahead of Oceania.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Scholars have attributed this to different factors including geography, climate,[14] corruption,[14] colonialism, the Cold War,[15][16] and neocolonialism.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Despite this low concentration of wealth.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;recent economic expansion and a large and young population make Africa an important economic market in the broader global context.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;and Africa has a large quantity of natural resources.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative commons</title>
      <link>https://nygma.pro/posts/creativecommons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:14:17 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nygma.pro/posts/creativecommons/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creative Commons (CC) is an American non-profit organization and international network devoted to educational access and expanding the range of creative works available for others to build upon legally and to share.[4] The organization has released several copyright licenses, known as Creative Commons licenses, free of charge to the public, to allow authors of creative works to communicate which rights they reserve and which rights they waive for the benefit of recipients or other creators. Content owners still maintain their copyright, but Creative Commons licenses give standard releases that replace the individual negotiations for specific rights between copyright owner (licensor) and licensee, that are necessary under an &amp;ldquo;all rights reserved&amp;rdquo; copyright management.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The City we all love</title>
      <link>https://nygma.pro/posts/nairobiway/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:02:31 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nygma.pro/posts/nairobiway/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To help understand why patent rights not only encourage inventors but also promote the wider diffusion of&#xA;new technology for the benefit of society, economic historians Naomi Lamoreaux and the late Kenneth&#xA;Sokoloff suggested the following thought experiment:&#xA;Imagine a world in which there was no patent system to guarantee inventors property rights to their&#xA;discoveries. In such a world, inventors would have every incentive to be secretive and to guard jealously their&#xA;discoveries from competitors [because those discoveries] could, of course, be copied with impunity. “By&#xA;contrast, in a world where property rights in invention were protected, the situation would be very different.&#xA;Inventors would now feel free to promote their discoveries as widely as possible so as to maximize returns&#xA;either from commercializing their ideas themselves or from [licensing] rights to the idea to others. The&#xA;protections offered by the patent system would thus be an important stimulus to the exchange of&#xA;technological information in and of themselves. Moreover, it is likely that the cross -fertilization that resulted&#xA;from these information flows would be a potent stimulus to technological change.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git in a nutshell</title>
      <link>https://nygma.pro/posts/collins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:13:31 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nygma.pro/posts/collins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So, what is Git in a nutshell? This is an important section to absorb, because if you understand what Git is and the fundamentals of how it works, then using Git effectively will probably be much easier for you. As you learn Git, try to clear your mind of the things you may know about other VCSs, such as CVS, Subversion or Perforce — doing so will help you avoid subtle confusion when using the tool.&#xA;Even though Git’s user interface is fairly similar to these other VCSs, Git stores and thinks about information in a very different way, and understanding these differences will help you avoid becoming confused while using it.&#xA;Snapshots,&#xA;Not Differences&#xA;The major difference between Git and any other VCS (Subversion and friends included) is the way Git thinks about its data. Conceptually, most other systems store information as a list of file-based&#xA;changes. These other systems (CVS, Subversion, Perforce, and so on) think of the information they store as a set of files and the changes made to each file over time (this is commonly described as&#xA;delta-based version control).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://nygma.pro/posts/trial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nygma.pro/posts/trial/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The “natural rights” theory.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;meanwhile, invokes another commonsense premise that most of us instinctively&#xA;hold to be true: that the product of mental labor is by all rights the property of its creator, no less than the&#xA;product of physical labor is the property of its creator&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(or of the person who purchases it from that creator).&#xA;This is what Daniel Webster was referring to when he said, “The American Constitution does not attempt to&#xA;give an inventor a right to their invention, or an author a right to his composition; it recognizes an original,&#xA;pre-existing, inherent right of property in such invention or composition.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
